{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "55 + 90",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 16",
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 39",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 94",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 79",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 18",
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 57",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 80",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 54",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 29",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 79",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 55",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 11",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 46",
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 77",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 91",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 81",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 15",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 87",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 49",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 39",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 80",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 33",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 25",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 43",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 66",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 11",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 15",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 68",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 41",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 16",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 51",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 97",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 82",
      "answer": 175
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 27",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 70",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 23",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 6",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 18",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 51",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 81",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 9",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 60",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 71",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 33",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 34",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 74",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 86",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 66",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 75",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 1",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 4",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 12",
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 19",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 32",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 25",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 83",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 2",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 55",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 29",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 21",
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 62",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 66",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 30",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 46",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 64",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 11",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 34",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 64",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 14",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 40",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 74",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 9",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 1",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 38",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 28",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 32",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 32",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 71",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 16",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 93",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 68",
      "answer": 162
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 78",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 22",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 1",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 39",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 67",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 9",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 87",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 19",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 21",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 47",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 42",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 57",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 5",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 45",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 14",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 20",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 46",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 58",
      "answer": 87
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 7,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 600,
      "to": 700
    }
  }
}